adaptedmind.com 2019-06-10

# AdaptedMind

**Introduction**  
AdaptedMind.com, owned and operated by GloWorld, LLC and its affiliates understand that your privacy is important to you. AdaptedMind is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and the personal information that you may provide as you access and use the materials on AdaptedMind.com (the "Site"), including the subscription pages of the Site. In this written Privacy Policy, AdaptedMind.com describes the scope and breadth of our commitment to privacy. AdaptedMind.com may, in its discretion, amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any material changes to our policy will be reflected on this page, so that you remain informed about the information we collect and how we use it. By exploring and using this Site, and by submitting information as you use this Site, you agree to GloWorld's use of such information as described herein. This Site may contain links to external sites, which sites are not governed by this privacy policy, and Glo does not take responsibility for the privacy practices of any third party sites to which we link. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any such sites before you submit information there.

**Information That We Collect, and How We Use It**  
AdaptedMind.com collects information from our users when they create their account for this Site, when they request copies of publications, seek additional information regarding our services or employment opportunities, or register for conferences and other GloWorld-sponsored events. Some of our Site's registration, enrollment, account setup and other forms may ask users to give us contact information, unique personal identifiers, financial information, subject areas of interest and/or demographic information. We may use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our Site. We sometimes aggregate demographic information, and the types of systems and browsers of users for internal purposes, so that we may better understand the user population of our Site, identify subject areas of interest, and determine whether the Site is designed to work with the computer settings of a majority of our visitors. GloWorld also may conduct user surveys on the Web, which usually are intended to provide GloWorld with information on a number of areas, such as user identity, user viewing habits, whether or not users found what they were searching for, whether the Site content is relevant to user needs, and the like. GloWorld uses the information gathered from such surveys to improve our web content, navigation, and overall visitor experience.

Any personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, subject areas of interest, etc., allows AdaptedMind.com to inform you about updates to the service and to notify you about other products and services offered by AdaptedMind.com that may be of interest to you. AdaptedMind.com also reserves the right to perform inter-school communications to facilitate the proper functioning of the site. We will not sell, share, or rent or otherwise make available any of that information to other parties, except that we may disclose the information to third parties who perform services on our behalf in connection with the Site and have a need to access the information in connection with those services. In addition, GloWorld may disclose contact information for you in response to inquiries by bona-fide rights owners in connection with allegations of infringement of copyright or other proprietary rights arising from information that you have posted on the Site or otherwise provided to GloWorld. Individuals that subscribe to e-mail newsletters are given the opportunity to opt-out of promotions, news, and information at the time of sign up. Our Site also provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the points where we request information. You may also feel free to contact us as indicated below.

**E-Mail Addresses**  
We may collect the e-mail addresses at the point of subscription, of users who wish to receive e-mail notification of publications and press releases in identified subject areas of interest, and of those who send us e-mail messages. We will not, however, share any e-mail addresses with any third party or send unsolicited e-mail to any of the addresses we collect, except in very limited circumstances as set forth in this policy.

**Student Information**  
We collect the student information, name and grade, for the purpose of customizing reports and progress in the AdaptedMind program. This information is not knowingly shared with any business partners or third parties.

We also collect student performance information as reasonably necessary for the student to participate in the AdaptedMind program. This includes but is not limited to the number of problems a student has answered correctly and incorrectly, their login session information, the content they have viewed and accumulated within the program. Individual performance information can be used for site features personal to the related parent account and their students and/or for internal business metric purposes. This information is not shared with other parents (not associated with the account) and their children, business partners or third parties.

**Cookies**  
GloWorld may use browser cookies on this Site to keep track of your visit to our Site. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent from a Web server to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Use of cookies may allow GloWorld to provide a higher quality, more relevant, customer experience. Use of cookies may also allow GloWorld to automate entry into password protected portions of the Site so that you will not need to re-enter your password each time you visit our Site. We may also use cookies to track which areas of the web site are most popular with our users and to further GloWorld's understanding concerning overall use of the site. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored on your computer. Please refer to your browser instructions or a help screen to learn more about these functions and how to use them. Please be advised that certain sections or functionalities of the Site may be inaccessible to you if your browser does not accept cookies.

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**International Transfer of Information**  
Because GloWorld is a global organization, information collected on this Site may be transferred from time to time among the GloWorld offices or personnel, or to third parties located throughout the world, including offices located outside the European Economic Area, and the Site may be viewed and hosted anywhere in the world, including countries that may not have laws regulating the use and transfer of personally-identifiable data. By using the Site and submitting information on it, you voluntarily consent to such international transfer and hosting of such information.

**Security Processes**  
GloWorld has in place technological and operational security processes designed to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. Only authorized employees and contractors will have access to any data provided by you, and that access is limited by need. Each employee or contractor having access to any personally-identifiable information is obligated to maintain its confidentiality. Although we take steps that are generally accepted as industry standard to protect your personally-identifiable information, GloWorld cannot guarantee that your personally-identifiable information will not become accessible to unauthorized persons.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
GloWorld is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any non-GloWorld web sites to which we link from this Site. Compliance With Law

**Legal Process**  
GloWorld complies with all applicable privacy laws and regulations. GloWorld may be compelled to surrender personal user or customer information to United States or other legal authorities without express user consent if presented with a court subpoena or similar legal order, or as required or permitted by the laws, rules and regulations of any nation, state or other applicable jurisdiction. Also, in the event of a violation of the terms and conditions of use of this Site or a violation of any restrictions on use of materials provided in or through this Site, we may disclose personal user information to our affected business partners or legal authorities.

**Change and/or Delete Information**  
You may access, correct, update, and/or delete any personally-identifiable information that you submit to this Site. To do so, please either follow instructions on the page of the Site on which you have provided such information or subscribed or registered or contact us.

**Performance**  

As a User uses the AdaptedMind.com curriculum, the site collects infomration about the User's performance. We use this information to better improve the User's experience, as well as in aggregate to improve our product. We will never, to any third party, disclose this information in a manner in which it can be linked or associated with the User's identity. Only authorized employees of AdaptedMind.com and its affiliates, the student User, and the authorized User that created the student's account can view both the identity and performance of the student User.

**Use of AdaptedMind.com**  
Your access to and use of the Site are subject to certain terms and conditions, which are summarized in our Terms and Conditions of Use.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or GloWorld's practices as we operate this Site, please contact us.
